Oh, that feels so good.
哇，這是真是舒服
Oh, lucky me. Coffee and a live sex show.
哎呀，我運氣真好 有咖啡喝還可以看現場性愛演出
- I'm sorry, what? - I'm sorry.
-不好意思，什麼呢？ -不好意思
- Nothing. I was just reading to Emma. - From Cosmo?
-沒事，我只是在唸書給艾□聽 -念《柯夢波丹》嗎？
Yeah. Yeah, it's:
是啊，是啊，是…
"Climax Your Way to Better Skin."
《讓你有更細緻的肌膚》
So I have to go shopping today, which is my least favorite thing.
我今天必須要去買衣服 這真是我最不喜歡做的事
I'm so bad at picking out clothes.
我實在是很不會挑選衣服
So you need someone who knows fashion to tell you what looks good.
所以你需要有很瞭解 時尚的人來給你建議
Not me. Not me. Not me.
不要是我，不要是我，不要是我
- Oh, hey, Rach? - Yeah?
-嘿，瑞秋？ -怎樣？
- Maybe you could take Charlie shopping? - Oh, well..
-或許你可以帶查莉去買衣服 -喔，嗯…
- I'm sure you have better things to do. - You kidding?
-你可能很忙沒空吧 -你在開玩笑嗎？
Rachel loves to shop, and she has great taste.
瑞秋愛死逛街了，而且她品味極佳
She's the one that taught me not to wear white after Labor Day..
就是她教我在勞工節之後 不要穿白色衣服
and to always, always, always put on underwear when trying on clothes.
而且永遠、永遠記住在試穿衣服時 一定要穿內衣褲
If you have the time, I'd really appreciate the help.
如果你有空，我會很感激你的幫忙的
Okay. Yeah, let's shop.
好的，好啊，我們逛街去
Okay, you are gonna come back with some very classy clothes.
好的，你一定會 買回來很多有格調的衣服
And some slutty lingerie. Slutty!
還有一些淫蕩的內衣，淫蕩喔！
Okay, great. All right, bye.
好的，太好了，拜拜
Pain in the ass!
超級討厭的！
- That's off, right? - What's the matter, Phoebe?
-已經掛掉了，對嗎？ -怎麼了？菲比
Mike's sister just invited me to a party tonight and he's gonna be there.
麥克的姐姐剛邀請我去今晚的派對 而且他也會去
She was like, "Don't worry. I asked him and he's totally okay with seeing you."
她說「別擔心，我問過他了 他完全不介意見到你」
So now I have to go so he'll think that I'm totally okay with seeing him.
所以現在我一定得去了 否則他會認為我很介意見到他
- Which you're not. You're hung up on him. - Exactly.
-你根本就很介意，你還沒有忘記他 -沒錯
You want him to eat his heart out, so you have to look fabulous.
你想要他懊悔不已 所以你一定要看起來艷光四射
I didn't even think about that.
我根本沒有那樣想過
Sexual politics!
性慾權術！
Phoebe, I'm taking Charlie shopping.
菲比，我要帶查莉去逛街
- Come and I'll help you find something. - That'd be great.
-一起來，我可以幫你挑衣服 -太棒了
Oh, isn't that nice? The three of you, trying on slutty lingerie together.
真是太好了，你們三個人 一起試穿淫蕩睡衣
- That's not what we're gonna do. - Why'd you ruin it? Who was I hurting?
-我們沒有要那樣做 -你為何要這麼說？我得罪誰了？
The One With The Donor
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Fortunately, she has a very pretty face.
哇，還好她長的很漂亮
I still can't believe this. My uterus is an inhospitable environment?
我還是無法相信 我的子宮是不適著床的環境？
I've always tried so hard to be a good hostess.
我一直都很努力想要當個稱職的女主人
I can't believe my sperm have low motility.
我不敢相信我的精子的活動力太低
While I was growing up, they sure seemed to be in a hurry to get places.
當我在長大的時候 它們倒是等不及要到處去遊玩
- Hi there. - Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
I'm sorry there wasn't better news from your tests last week..
關於你們上星期的測試 我很抱歉，沒有什麼更好的消息
but I wanted to talk to you about your options.
但是我想要跟你們談談你們可有的選擇
Okay.
好的
Even though your chances of conceiving through natural means aren't great..
雖然你們以正常方式 受孕的機率很低…
you never know, so keep having sex on a regular basis.
但是很難定論的 所以你們還是持續進行性生活
Oh, damn it!
哎，是喔！
Don't worry. After a while, you'll tune it out.
別擔心，等一下你就會習慣了
Given your situation, the options with the greatest chances for success..
在這種情況之下，最佳的選擇就是…
would be surrogacy or insemination using a sperm donor.
代理孕母或是經由捐贈精子受孕
If you feel that neither of those is right for you, you could always adopt.
如果你們認為上述兩種選擇都不適合 你們還是可以選擇領養
Is that a hint?
這是個暗示嗎？
Because we love you, Dr. Connelly, but we don't want you to be our child.
我們是挺熱愛你的，唐納利醫生 但是我們不想要領養你
Wow! Talk about an inhospitable environment.
糟糕！說的話還真不受歡迎
Hi. Okay, you ready to go pick up Phoebe and go shopping?
嗨，你準備好要去接菲比逛街了嗎？
- Let's do it. - All right, have a good time.
-我們走吧 -好的，祝你們逛的愉快
Not gonna find any clothes in there.
那裡面是找不到衣服的
- Hey, you guys. - Hi.
-你們好 -嗨
Guess who's up for keynote speaker at the National Paleontology Conference?
猜猜看誰是 全國古生物學大會的主講人？
- Chris Bailey? - Yeah, right.
-克裡斯培利嗎？ -對啊，是啊
When was the last time he made a submission deadline for an abstract?
他上次準時提交摘要是什麼時候呢？
Why are you laughing?
你為什麼要笑呢？
Just seeing what it'd be like to be a paleontologist.
只是想瞭解一下 當古生物學家是怎樣的
It's fun. Yeah.
真好玩，是啊
So you're up for keynote speaker?
所以你要當主講人？
- Who's deciding? - Professor Sherman.
-是誰做的決定呢？ -薛曼教授
- I'm meeting with him today. - He's a pretty tough guy to impress.
-我今天要跟他見面 -他是個蠻難伺候的人
I think I know how to dazzle him.
我想我知道要怎麼迷惑他
You're not gonna to do a magic trick, are you?
你應該不是要變魔術吧？
No.
不是
- Hey, guys. - I want to ask you something.
-大家好 -我想要問你們一個問題
I may get to speak at this paleontology convention.
我可能會在這個古生物學大會演說
If I do, I'd love for you guys to come and hear me.
如果是這樣 我想邀請你們來聽我的演講
I think I can safely say that we all have family issues, work and/or are sick.
我想如果說我們都有家庭 工作或是身體不適等理由是沒錯的
- It's in Barbados. - But you come first.
-是在巴貝多 -但是你是最重要的
I'm there.
我去定了
- I don't know Ross, I'm not feeling too.. - Barbados is in the Caribbean, Joe.
-我不知道，羅斯，我不是覺得很… -巴貝多是在加勒比海，喬伊
Why didn't anybody say so?
為什麼沒有人說呢？
- See you later. - Okay, bye.
-待會見 -好的，拜
- Bye. See you. - Bye.
-拜，再見 -拜
- So how did it go at the fertility clinic? - Not as much fun as last time.
-驗孕診所怎麼說？ -不像上次一樣好玩
Apparently, you only get porn if you're giving a sperm sample.
很明顯地，他們只有在采精子樣本時 才會給你看色情書刊
So, what did the doctor say?
那醫生怎麼說呢？
There's surrogacy, but Monica's dreamt her whole life of carrying a child..
可以用代理孕母，但摩妮卡這一輩子 都在夢想懷孕…
and she just felt that watching a surrogate would be too hard for her.
而她會覺得看著代理孕母懷孕 對她而言會太難受了
- So you're ruling out surrogacy? - Yeah.
-所以你們不考慮代理孕母？ -沒錯
So I don't have to learn what that means?
所以我不用知道那是什麼意思囉？
Aside from adoption, the only other choice is insemination..
除了領養外，剩下的選擇 就是接受精子捐贈
so we're talking about sperm donors.
所以我們現在在討論精子捐贈者的事
Enough said. I'm there for you, man. Where is she, upstairs?
夠了，我隨時為你效勞，兄弟 她在哪？樓上嗎？
Your long-standing offer to have sex with my wife is appreciated.
我是非常感激 你長期以來想跟我老婆上床的好意
- But I think I'll pass. - So how do you feel about all this?
-但是我想我心領了 -那你的感覺呢？
I wish there was an easier way for us to have a child, but there isn't one.
我真希望我們有更簡單的方式可生孩子 但是我們並沒有選擇
Come on, Ross, be a good guy. Step up and do it.
別這樣，羅斯，做做好人 挺身而出吧
What?
什麼？
What?! No! I'm not gonna give them Ben!
什麼？不！ 我不會把班給他們的！
The data we're receiving from MRI scans and DNA testing..
我們從磁共振造影跟脫氧核糖核酸測試 所取得的化石…
of these fossils are staggering.
資料數據是很驚人的
I mean, we've been accepting Leakey's dates as a given.
我的意思是我們一直以來都將 李奇年代法視為理所當然
But if they're off by even a 100,000 years or so..
但是如果它的誤差 即使只有十萬年左右…
then you can just throw most of our assumptions..
那你可以捨棄我們大部分推論…
you know, right in the trash.
你知道的，丟到垃圾桶裡
So, what I'm saying is..
所以，我要說的是…
Is that..
是…
Is that repercussions could be huge.
是所受影響的後果是很大的
I mean, not just in paleontology, but if you think about it..
我是說，不只是在古生物學 但是如果你仔細想想…
in evolutionary biology, genetics, geology.
甚至是在進化生物學、基因學、地質學
I mean, truly, the mind boggles.
我是說，真的，無限想像的空間
Well, that's not what you want.
嗯，結果不該是這樣的
- Incentive for Men? - I'll take some of that.
-男人的動機？ -我要噴一點
- Phoebe, that's for men. - I know.
-菲比，那是男生的香水 -我知道
When I go to the party later..
在我等一下去派對時…
Mike will know I'm over him because I'll smell like another guy.
麥克會知道我已經忘了他了 因為我聞起來會有另一個男人的味道
Okay.
好了
Oh, good, I'm dating a Russian cabdriver.
太好了，我在跟俄羅斯計程車司機約會
Seriously, does anyone buy this? I smell like beets.
拜託，有人買這個嗎？ 這聞起來像是甜菜
I really like those jackets with the shoulder pads in them. Where are those?
我真的很喜歡那些有墊肩的外套 在哪邊有呢？
On Melanie Griffith in Working Girl.
梅蘭妮葛麗芬在《上班女郎》裡面穿的
I think what you want is over here.
我想你適合穿的在這邊
See, I told you I needed someone.
我就知道 我需要有人幫我
By the way, as a thank you, I would really love to take you out.
對了，為了要謝謝你 我真的很想請你吃飯
- Really? - Joey and I are going to a movie tonight.
-真的嗎？ -喬伊跟我今晚要去看電影
- You want to come? - Oh, I can't.
-你想要一起去嗎？ -我不行
Because I've seen them.
因為我看過了
You've seen all the movies?
你已經看過所有的電影了？
Yeah. I'm a big fan.
是啊，我為之入迷
Of the movies.
電影迷
You know, motion pictures.
所有的電影
The talkies.
包括老電影
Rach, will you come with me to a dressing room?
瑞秋，你可以跟我進去試衣間試穿嗎？
- Sure. - Okay.
-當然 -好的
Maybe we could do something else.
或許我們可以做別的事
You know, that depends on what it is. I've done a lot of stuff.
你知道的，那要看是什麼事 很多東西我都做過了
So, what were you doing out there? Do you not like Charlie?
你剛剛是怎麼了？ 你不喜歡查莉嗎？
She's okay. I don't know, I just don't get a really good vibe from her.
她還好啦，我不知道 我只是跟她不投緣吧
- Why? - I don't know.
-為什麼？ -我不知道
You know, just the way she waltzed in here all smart..
你知道的，只是她的一舉一動 聰明的要命…
and tall, you know..
而且又高挑，你知道的…
and just swept Joey off his feet. Nobody else has a chance.
然後又把喬伊迷的東倒西歪的 別人都沒有機會
- Who else? - Anybody.
-還有誰呢？ -任何人啊
You. Me.
你，我
You know, Monica's mom.
你知道的，摩妮卡的媽
You like Joey?!
你喜歡喬伊？
Phoebe!
菲比！
All right, look, I do. I have a little thing for him. Just..
好吧，你說的沒錯 我對他是有點感覺，只是…
- Oh, my God. - It's just physical.
-喔，我的天啊 -是肉慾的
I have it totally under control, okay? It's just when I see them together..
我已經完全控制住了，好嗎？ 只是當我看到他們在一起…
sometimes, I just get a little jealous.
有時候，我就會有點忌妒
Wow. Isn't that ironic that he liked you, and now you like..?
哇，好諷刺喔，他以前喜歡過你 然後現在你喜歡…
I get it!
我知道！
All right, as long as it's under control.
好吧，一切都控制住就好了
You can't do anything about it. He's already dating her.
你不可以採取任何行動 他已經跟她在一起了
She is a nice person. That wouldn't be right.
她是個好人，那是不對的
I know, I know. So it's just not a big deal.
我知道，我知道，所以沒事啦
- So can we keep this between us? -Sure.
-你可以不要說出去嗎？ -當然
Great, because I gotta get out of here. The smell of beets is killing me.
太好了，因為我得出去了 我快被甜菜味熏死了
Any chance Charlie has a deaf twin?
查莉可能會有耳聾的雙胞胎妹妹嗎？
- Hi, honey. - Hey.
-嗨，親愛的 -嘿
I brought a friend home for dinner. This is Zack from work.
我帶個朋友回來吃晚餐 這是我同事柴克
Oh, of course. It's so nice to see you again, Zack.
當然啦，很高興再見到你，柴克
- You too. - You guys haven't actually met before.
-我也是 -你們並沒有見過面
But, boy, you're both polite.
天啊，你們還真有禮貌
Have a seat. I'll get you a beer.
請坐，我幫你拿啤酒
- I got it. - Thanks.
-我來拿 -謝謝
- So Zack's pretty nice, huh? - Yeah, I guess.
-柴克不錯吧？ -是啊，應該吧
So how would you like to have a baby that's half yours and half his?
那你想不想要跟他生個小孩呢？
Excuse me?
什麼？
We're talking about sperm donors, and Zack may be the guy.
我們在講的是精子捐贈者 而柴克或許就是適當的人選
Look. He's intelligent, he's healthy, he's athletic. I mean, he's sperm-tastic!
他很聰明、健康、體格強壯 我是說，他是最佳人選了！
Chandler, this is crazy. Well, what did you even say to him?
錢德，這太瘋狂了 你是怎麼跟他說的？
"Come up. Meet my wife. Give us your sperm."
「上來看看我老婆 給我們你的精子」
I invited him to dinner so you'd get a chance to get to know him.
我邀請他來吃晚餐讓你見見他
With a sperm bank, you never meet the guy, get to check him out.
如果是精子銀行 我們根本不能見到那個捐贈者
- Chandler! - I'm telling you, he's great.
-錢德！ -我告訴你，他棒透了
I mean, even if my sperm worked fine, I think he'd be the way to go.
我是說，即使我的精子沒有問題 我也認為我們應該選擇他
I'm not going to be a part of this.
我不要淌這趟渾水
You can't bring some random guy home and expect him to be our sperm donor.
你不能隨便帶個男的回來 當精子捐贈者
Okay.
好吧
- Zack? - Thanks.
-柴克 -謝謝
Do you have a coaster? I don't want to make a ring.
你有杯墊嗎？我不想留下杯印
Tell me about yourself, Zack.
多聊聊你自己，柴克
Oh, God, do you think she heard? It'd be so bad if she heard.
天啊，你覺得她聽到了嗎？ 如果她聽到就慘了
Maybe she didn't hear. I'll go into that dressing room and talk. You stay here.
或許她沒有聽到，我到隔壁間說話 你待在這裡
- See if you can hear me. - Okay, great.
-看看你是不是可以聽到我說話 -好的
Oh, thank God, I can't hear a word that you're saying.
喔，感謝上帝，我聽不到你說話
- I didn't say anything yet. - Well, get back in there and talk.
-我還沒有開始說話 -那回去裡面然後說話啊
I'm Rachel.
我是瑞秋
It's so annoying when I put Emma on the phone to talk with my friends.
讓艾□在電話上跟我朋友講話 真的很討厭
What?
什麼？
Well, some things are just hard to say to your face.
嗯，有些事是很難當你的面說的
Okay, well, I heard that. Which means that she heard it too.
好吧，我聽到了，表示她也聽到了
- We have a problem. - Oh, what are we gonna do?
-我們有麻煩了 -喔，我們該怎麼辦呢？
Just be honest with her.
就老實跟她說吧
Oh, my God!
喔，我的天啊！
It is annoying when parents put babies on the phone.
父母讓嬰兒聽電話 的確是很討厭
All right, enough out of you!
好了，你說夠了！
Thank you.
謝謝
Where did I go wrong? This is good stuff.
我是哪裡做錯了？這是很好的東西啊
- Hello? - I need to talk to Charlie. Is she there?
-哈囉？ -我要跟查莉講話，她在嗎？
No, she went shopping with Rachel. Why? What's up?
不在，她跟瑞秋去逛街了 為什麼？怎麼了？
I'm meeting with Professor Sherman about my being the keynote speaker.
我正在跟薛曼教授 討論關於我當主講人的事
- How's it going? - It could be better.
-進行的如何呢？ -可以更順利的
He fell asleep.
他睡著了
What? But I already bought my ticket to Bermuda!
什麼？但是我已經 訂了到百慕達的機票了！
- Barbados. - Fine, I'll rent a car and drive.
-是巴貝多 -好啦，我再租車開過去
You have to get that job.
你一定要得到這工作
What am I supposed to do? He's out cold.
我應該怎麼辦呢？他完全睡著了
In fact, he was just talking in his sleep before..
事實上，剛剛他還在說夢話
and evidently he wants someone named Fran to "spank him harder."
而且他還要一個叫法蘭的人 「再打用力點」
- Well, just wake him up. - I can't.
-那叫醒他吧 -我不行
If he realizes that I'm the one who put him to sleep, I won't get the job.
如果他發現我是讓他睡著的人 我就得不到這個工作了
That's a tough one.
那倒是挺難的
Oh, wait a minute. This happened to me before.
等等，這以前也發生在我身上過
Yeah, I was auditioning for a play, and the producer fell asleep. I..
是啊，我之前在試演一齣戲劇的時候 那個製作人睡著了，我…
No, wait a minute.
不，等等
It was me who fell asleep.
其實是我睡著了
I mean, hey, Shakespeare, how about a chase scene once in a while?
我是說，莎士比亞 來點動作場面吧？
- Hey, guys, dinner's ready. - I'm gonna go wash up first.
-嘿，晚餐好了 -我先去洗手
Thanks.
謝了
What do you think? I want his genes for my kid. Those eyes, those cheekbones.
你覺得呢？我要我的孩子有他的基因 那雙眼睛，那顴骨
Okay, there's enthusiastic, and there's just plain gay.
好了，可能是過度狂熱 也有可能是同志
- You don't like him. - I think he's fine.
-你不喜歡他 -我想他不錯
But we don't know anything real about him.
但是我們對他瞭解不夠
- I wish we could get more information. - All right, just follow my lead.
-我希望我們可以知道多一點 -好的，跟著我的話鋒轉
- You guys have a great place here. - Thanks. I'm crazy about our place.
-你們家真是好棒 -謝謝，我很喜歡這地方
Hey, speaking of crazy..
嘿，說到瘋狂…
do you have a history of mental illness in the family?
你們家有遺傳性精神疾病嗎？
No. Although, I did have an uncle who voted for Dukakis.
沒有，但是我是有個叔叔 投票給杜凱吉斯
That's really not the kind of thing we're looking for.
那真的不是我們所希望看到的
Okay.
好的
So tell me, how'd you guys meet?
告訴我，你們是怎麼認識的呢？
Oh, friends first, drunk in London, you know the story.
剛開始是朋友，在倫敦喝醉，你知道的
I've got a better question for you:
我有個更棒的問題要問你
Do you or any of your blood relatives have diabetes?
你或是你的血親 有人有糖尿病嗎？
No.
沒有
Heart disease? Alzheimer's? Gout?
心臟病？阿茲海默症？痛風？
You guys don't have people for dinner a lot, huh?
你們不常請朋友到家裡用餐，是嗎？
We're just making conversation.
我們只是在找話題聊聊
Yeah, well, okay. I heard a joke today. It's pretty funny.
好吧，我今天聽到一個笑話 真的是挺好笑的
You know what's not funny? Male pattern baldness.
你知道有什麼是不好笑的嗎？ 雄性禿頭
You guys have shown a lot of interest in me tonight, and I'm flattered..
你們今晚對我很有興趣，我很受寵若驚
and quite frankly, a little frightened.
而且老實說，是有點受驚
Can we just talk about something else?
我們可以聊聊別的話題嗎？
- Sure. - All right.
-當然 -好的
This ravioli's delicious.
這個意大利水餃真是美味
I notice you're enjoying that ravioli with a beautiful set of teeth.
我發現你享用那水餃的牙齒真是整齊
Did you have braces as a child?
你小時候有戴牙套嗎？
- No, I didn't. - Yes!
-不，沒有 -太好了！
We're teeth people, Zack.
我們很重視牙齒的，柴克
Let's just do it. Let's just go over there and see if she heard.
我們過去問她有沒有聽到
- Good plan. - Okay.
-好主意 -好的
- What? Where are you going? - Oh, I'm sorry, Rachel.
-什麼？你是在做什麼呢？ -對不起，瑞秋
I don't have time for your childish games, okay?
我沒有時間玩你的幼稚遊戲，好嗎？
I still have to find something incredible to wear..
我還得要找到很驚艷的衣服穿
so I can beat Mike at "Who's More Over Who"!
那我才可以在「誰先忘了誰」上 打敗麥克！
- Where have you been? - Trying on clothes.
-你好 -你好
-你去哪裡了？ -去試穿衣服
Oh, really? In the dressing room? Well, that's so weird.
真的嗎？在試衣間嗎？喔，真奇怪
Phoebe and I were in the dressing room. Gosh, it's just such a small world.
菲比跟我剛剛也在試衣間 天啊，這世界真是小
Rachel, I heard you two guys whispering.
瑞秋，我聽到你們倆的對談了
Oh, God, you did, you heard. Okay, look, let me explain.
天啊，你聽到了 好的，聽著，讓我解釋
There's nothing to explain. I heard you.
沒有必要解釋，我都聽到了
Phoebe likes Joey.
菲比喜歡喬伊
Yeah.
是啊
I don't understand it. I mean, Phoebe likes Joey..
我不明白，我是說菲比喜歡喬伊
and then she's here to buy a dress to impress another guy?
可是她卻來買衣服 來驚艷另一個男人？
Yeah, that's Phoebe. That's Phoebe. You know, she just wants them all.
是啊，菲比就是那樣，她就是那樣 你知道的，她就是全部都要
It's, like, she's nympho.
那就像是女色情狂
- Wow! - Yeah.
-哇！ -是啊
You know, by the way, I heard you tell her not to do anything.
對了，我有聽到你告訴她 不可以做任何事
Thanks for sticking up for me. God, you are such a nice person.
謝謝你替我說話 天啊，你真是個好人
I try.
我盡量
Oh, my God, you really want me to be the keynote speaker?
我的天啊 你真的要我當主講人嗎？
Thank you!
謝謝你！
You're welcome.
不用客氣
Wow! You look..
哇！你看起來…
stop-eating hot!
真是辣得讓人不想吃東西！
Which is like the highest level of hotness.
這是最高級別的辣耶
Okay, are you sure? Because I am really dreading going to this party.
你確定嗎？ 因為我真的很不想去這派對
Then don't go.
那就別去啊
Mike knows I'm coming. If I don't show up, he'll think it's because of him..
麥克知道我要去，如果我沒出現 他會以為那是因為他…
and then I'm gonna lose face. That's a very serious thing in my culture.
我那樣就會很沒面子 這對我來說是很嚴重的事
All right, then you go to that party, and you pretend to be over Mike.
好吧，那就去派對吧 然後假裝已經完全不受麥克影響
Afterward, you come to my place and I'll get you good and drunk.
之後你再來我家 我再幫你好好借酒解愁
You got it. Okay.
沒問題，好的
But not on the wine that you made, okay?
但是不要喝你自己釀的酒好嗎？
Because I just don't want to go back to the emergency room.
因為我不想要再進急診室了
I'm sorry, I don't seem to have enough cash.
我很抱歉，我沒有足夠的現金
You would accept rubles, would you?
你可以接受盧布不是嗎？
This is a hundred-thousand-ruble note, which is worth approximately..
這是張面額十萬的盧布 大約的價值是…
nothing.
零
- David? - Phoebe! Hi.
-大衛？ -菲比！嗨
- Oh, my God! - Hi.
-喔，我的天！ -嗨
Wow! You look unbelievable.
哇！你看起來真是漂亮極了
Oh, yeah, well..
喔，是啊，嗯…
What are you doing here?
你在這裡做什麼呢？
Well, I'm back from Minsk. Permanently.
我從明斯克回來了，永久地
Well, what happened?
發生什麼事呢？
Remember how I was trying to achieve..
記得我正在嘗試製造…
the positronic distillation of subatomic particles?
次原子陽電子淨化嗎？
Yeah.
是啊
Well, after eight years of research, I discovered..
在經過八年的研究之後，我發現…
that it can't be done.
那是做不到的
- Oh, I'm sorry. - It's all right.
-很抱歉 -沒關係
This kind of thing happens all the time in science.
這種事在科學界常發生在…
To people who base eight years of research on a typo in a scientific journal.
尤其是因為科學期刊上一個誤刊 而用八年時間研究的人來說
Well..
嗯…
great that you're back. How are you?
你終於回來了真是好，你好嗎？
- Good. Good. Life is good. - Good.
-很好，過的還不錯 -很好
Well, I'm seeing someone.
我現在有交往的對象了
- Good for you. - Yeah.
-這樣啊，恭喜你了 -是啊
She's also a scientist, so she's very smart and pretty and..
她也是科學家，很聰明也很漂亮
It's actually because of you that we're together.
而且事實上是因為你 我們才在一起的
I mean, I saw what you had with that Mike guy..
我是說，我看到你跟那個麥克在一起
and I just said, "Boy, I want that."
然後我告訴自己 「天啊，我也想要那樣」
- Mike and I broke up. - You're kidding me.
-麥克跟我分手了 -你在開玩笑吧
Because I'm not seeing anybody. I just totally made that up.
因為我沒有在跟誰交往 我完全是編出來的
- Really? - I don't know why, I'm sorry.
-真的嗎？ -我不知道為什麼，我很抱歉
I guess I just didn't want to lose face.
我猜我只是不想沒面子
I understand.
我能瞭解
Yeah. Okay. So then, okay..
是啊，好的，那…
So we're both living in New York, not seeing anyone.
我們都住在紐約 沒有交往對像
- That's so not like us. - Yeah, I know.
-這太不像我們了 -是啊，我知道
Well, this is probably a stupid question, seeing that you look like that..
嗯，這或許是個蠢問題 看到你穿這樣…
but do you have someplace that you need to be right now?
但是你現在有要去什麼地方嗎？
Well..
嗯…
No.
沒有
- Well, do you want to get a drink? - I'd love to.
-那你想不想去喝點東西呢？ -我很想
- Great. - Okay.
-太棒了 -好的
Do you smell beets?
你有聞到甜菜味嗎？
All right, stay upwind of me.
好吧，站到我的逆風邊
Hey, there's Phoebe. Is that Mike she's with?
嘿，那是菲比，那是麥克嗎？
No, that's David.
不是，那是大衛
There's a third guy?
還有第三個男人？
Tip of the iceberg.
只是冰山的一角
I'm gonna take off now.
我現在要走了
You're gonna let me go home, aren't you?
你們會讓我回家嗎？
Sure you don't want to stay a little longer?
你確定不要再多坐一下嗎？
No, I should get home. I'm kind of tired.
不了，我應該要回家了，我有點累
Are you always tired?
你很容易累嗎？
Because that could be a sign of clinical depression.
因為這很有可能是憂鬱症的前兆
No, it's tiring to figure out the age at which all my grandparents died.
不，只是要想出我祖父母 是幾歲過世的讓我很累
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay.
-明天見 -好的
Bye.
再見
I think we found our sperm.
我想我們找到我們的精子了
He does seem pretty perfect.
他看起來是挺完美的
Yeah? You think so? Should I ask him?
你也這麼認為嗎？我要開口問他嗎？
No.
不要
Why not? Just because his great-grandmother was obese?
為什麼呢？ 就只因為他曾祖母有肥胖症嗎？
Our kid's gonna get that from you anyway.
反正我們的孩子也是會從你那遺傳到
No, that's not it.
不，不是那個緣故
It's just that when we were asking him all those questions before..
只是在我們問他那些問題時…
I just realized I don't care if he is the most perfect guy in the world.
我認識到我不在乎 他是不是世上最完美的男人
- He's not you. - Yeah, he's better!
-他不是你 -是啊，他比我更好！
No, he's not.
不，他不是
If I can't get pregnant with you, then I don't want to get pregnant by him..
如果我不能跟你懷孕，我也不想跟他…
or anyone else.
或是跟任何人
- Really? Are you sure? - Yeah, I'm sure.
-真的？你確定嗎？ -是的，我確定
Thank God, because l don't wanna do this either.
感謝上帝，因為我也不想這樣做
I was just doing it because I thought that was what you wanted.
我會這樣做 是因為我以為你想這樣
I'm the husband. I'm supposed to bring the sperm.
我是丈夫，我理當要提供精子的
That is so sweet.
這實在是很體貼
I love you.
我愛你
So you know this leaves us with..
所以你知道我們唯一的選擇就是…
Adoption.
領養
How do you feel about that?
你覺得如何呢？
I think I feel okay about it.
我想我沒問題
Actually, I think I feel really good about it.
事實上我覺得非常的好
Me too.
我也是
I wanna find a baby that needs a home, and I wanna raise it with you.
我想找到一個需要家庭溫暖的小孩 然後跟你一起撫養他
And I wanna mess it up in our own specific way.
然後我想用我們自己的方式來亂養他
So this is it? We're really gonna adopt?
這就是決定嗎？我們真的要領養？
Yeah.
是的
- Oh, my God! We're gonna be parents! - We are gonna be great parents.
-我的天！我們要當父母親了！ -我們會是很棒的父母
And it could be soon.
而且可能會很快
I mean, think about it. Right now, somewhere out there..
我是說，想想看 就是現在，在外面某個地方…
our baby could be being conceived.
我們的孩子可能正被受孕
Wait. If we're lucky, and we're really, really, really quiet..
等等，如果我們夠幸運 而且我們真的、真的、真的很安靜…
we may be able to hear the sound of a condom breaking.
我們或許可以聽到保險套破裂的聲音
Hey, Zack.
嘿，柴克
Hey, Chandler.
嘿，錢德
I wanted to apologize for last night.
我想為昨晚的事道歉
I got the feeling we made you uncomfortable.
我感到我們讓你很不舒服
- No, you didn't. - Really?
-不，並沒有 -真的嗎？
No, you did.
沒錯，你們是有
My wife and I have some boundary issues.
我老婆跟我越界了
Sometimes we ask inappropriate questions.
有時候我們會問些很不適當的問題
We're working on it.
我們正在改進中
- Here are the boards for Friday's pitch. - Thank you.
-這些是星期五推銷會的看板 -謝謝
You wouldn't know if Jeanette's planning on keeping her baby, would you?
你知不知道珍娜 是否要留著她的孩子？